Guide to the Ray Lyman Wilbur, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0064A
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- 1938-1939, Series 23
  - Hartford Board of Trustees (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - He (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - History (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Hitler Awards (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Ho (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - Hoover War Library (includes photographs) (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 209, Folder 14)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Timothy (Box 209, Folder 13)
  - Houses of Sali (Box 209, Folder 15)
  - Hydro phonics (Box 209, Folder 16)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education Men (Box 209, Folder 17)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education Men (Box 209, Folder 18)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education Women (Box 209, Folder 19)
  - I (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Internal Revenue (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - J (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Jews (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Journalism (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Junior Colleges (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Ka (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - Ki (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - La (Box 210, Folder 10)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - Law (Box 210, Folder 11)
  - Letters, School of (Box 210, Folder 12)
  - Li (Box 210, Folder 13)
  - Library (Box 210, Folder 14)
  - Library (Box 210, Folder 15)
  - Library (Box 210, Folder 16)
  - Library (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Library (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Ma (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Mathematics (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Mc (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Me (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Medical School, September (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Medical School, October (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Medical School, November (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Medical School, December (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Medical School, January (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Medical School, February (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Medical School, March (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Medical School, April (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Medical School, May (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Medical School, June (Box 213, Folder 10)
  - Medical School, July (Box 213, Folder 11)
  - Medical School, August (Box 213, Folder 12)
  - Medical School Auxiliary to Stanford Clinics (Box 213, Folder 14)
  - Medical School Institute of Industrial Hygiene (Box 213, Folder 13)
  - Medical Society of the State of California (Box 213, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Church (Box 213, Folder 18)
  - Men's Council (Box 213, Folder 19)
  - Mi (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Miogenic Lab (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Mo (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Museum (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Music (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - N (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - National (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - National (Box 214, Folder 9)
  - Nursing (Box 213, Folder 16)
  - O (Box 214, Folder 10)
  - Pa (Box 214, Folder 11)
  - Pa (Box 214, Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 214, Folder 13)
  - Passes (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Patents (Box 219, Folder 13)
  - Pensions (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Philosophy (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Physics (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Physics (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Physiology (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Pi Q (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Political Science (Box 220, Folder 10)
  - President's Office (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Psychology (Box 220, Folder 12)
  - Publicity (Box 220, Folder 13)
  - Q (Box 220, Folder 14)
  - Quad (Box 220, Folder 15)
  - Questionnaires (Box 220, Folder 16)
  - Ra (Box 220, Folder 17)
  - Radio (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Radio (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Radio (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Radio (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Recommendation, Letters of (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Registrar (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Requests for President's Reports (Box 220, Folder 11)
  - Requisitions, Travel Fund Completed (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Requisitions, Travel Fund No Funds (Box 221, Folder 9)
  - Requisitions, Travel Fund Pending (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 221, Folder 11)
  - Rice, Jack (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - Ro (Box 221, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 221, Folder 13)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 221, Folder 14)
  - Sa (Box 221, Folder 15)
  - San Francisco (Box 221, Folder 16)
  - Sc (Box 221, Folder 17)
  - Se (Box 221, Folder 18)
  - Slavic (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Sm (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Social Sciences Research Council (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - St (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Association, March, April, May (Box 222, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Association, June, July, August (Box 222, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Association (1 of 4) (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Association (2 of 4) (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Association (3 of 4) (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Association (4 of 4) (Box 222, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 222, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Fund (1 of 3) (Box 222, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Fund (2 of 3) (Box 222, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Fund (3 of 3) (Box 222, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Glee Club (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Stanford War Memorial (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Statistics (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Student Affairs (Box 215, Folder 11)
  - Student Hospital Fund (Box 213, Folder 17)
  - Su (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - T (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Trustees (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - Trustees (Box 223, Folder 11)
  - Tuition (Box 223, Folder 12)
  - U V (Box 223, Folder 13)
  - United States (Box 223, Folder 14)
  - Wa (Box 223, Folder 15)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Wh (Box 223, Folder 16)
  - Wo (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Women's Council (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - YMCA (Box 224, Folder 4)
- 1939-1940, Series 24
  - A.M.A Committee on Graduate Medical Education (Box 232, Folder 18)
  - A.M.A Council on Medical Education and Hospitals (1) (Box 232, Folder 16)
  - A.M.A Council on Medical Education and Hospitals (2) (Box 232, Folder 17)
  - American Medical Association, September - November (Box 232, Folder 12)
  - American Medical Association, December - February (Box 232, Folder 13)
  - American Medical Association, March - May (Box 232, Folder 14)
  - American Medical Association, June - August (Box 232, Folder 15)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, September, October (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, November, December (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, March, April (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, May, June (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, July, August (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - American Social Hygiene Association (1), January, February (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - American Social Hygiene Association (2), January, February (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Assistants (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Assistants (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Assistants (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Associated Students (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Ba (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Bacteriology (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Ballots - Committee on Presidency (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Ballots - New President (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Be (Box 225, Folder 9)
  - Bequests (Box 225, Folder 10)
  - Bi (Box 225, Folder 11)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 225, Folder 12)
  - Biology, School of (Box 225, Folder 13)
  - Board of Athletic Control [call slip - folder out/missing] (Box 225, Folder 14)
  - Br (Box 225, Folder 15)
  - Bu (Box 225, Folder 16)
  - Ca (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - California Physicians Service (1) (Box 233, Folder 11)
  - California Physicians Service (2) (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - California Society for Promotion of Medical Research (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - California, Emergency Relief (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - California, University of (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Foundation, September - February (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Foundation, March - August (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Institute of Washington (Box 226, Folder 8)
  - Ch (Box 226, Folder 9)
  - Chaparral (Box 226, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry (Box 226, Folder 11)
  - Civil Aeronautics (Pilot training program) (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Classical Literature (Box 226, Folder 13)
  - Co (Box 226, Folder 14)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (Box 226, Folder 15)
  - Comm. Conference on Higher Education ("Steering Committee Conference on Higher Education") (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Commencement (Box 226, Folder 16)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 226, Folder 17)
  - Communism (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Comptroller (1 of 3), June, July, August (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Comptroller (2 of 3), June, July, August (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller (3 of 3), June, July, August (Box 227, Folder 10)
  - Comptroller (1), September, October, November (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Comptroller (1), December, January, February (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller (1), March, April, May (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller (2), September, October, November (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Comptroller (2), December, January, February (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller (2), March, April, May (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Conventions (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Da (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Dean of Women (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - Dean of Men (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Do (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - Dormitories (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - E (Box 229, Folder 11)
  - Economics (Box 228, Folder 8)
  - Education (Box 228, Folder 9)
  - Education Commission on Resources (Box 228, Folder 14)
  - Education, School of, September - November (Box 228, Folder 10)
  - Education, School of, December - February (Box 228, Folder 11)
  - Education, School of, March - May (Box 228, Folder 12)
  - Education, School of, June - August (Box 228, Folder 13)
  - Encina Hall (Box 228, Folder 15)
  - Endowment (Box 228, Folder 16)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Guggenheim lab.) (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, Military Science and Tactics (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Engineering, Mining and Metallurgy (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - English (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - English - Speech and Drama (1) (Box 229, Folder 9)
  - English - Speech and Drama (2) (Box 229, Folder 10)
  - Fa (Box 229, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Housing (Box 229, Folder 13)
  - Fellowships - Miscellaneous (Box 229, Folder 14)
  - Fo (Box 229, Folder 15)
  - Food Research Institute (1) (Box 229, Folder 16)
  - Food Research Institute (2) (Box 229, Folder 17)
  - Fraternities (Box 229, Folder 18)
  - Friends of Music Fund (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - Ga (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - General Education Board (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Geology (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Germanic Languages (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Gi (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Gr (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 230, Folder 8)
  - Graphic Art (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - Haq (Box 230, Folder 11)
  - Har (Box 230, Folder 12)
  - He (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - History (Box 230, Folder 14)
  - Ho (Box 230, Folder 15)
  - Hoover Library on War, Revolution, and Peace (Box 230, Folder 16)
  - Hoover Library on War, Revolution, and Peace (Box 230, Folder 17)
  - Hoover Library on War, Revolution, and Peace (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Library on War, Revolution, and Peace (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Timothy (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Houses for Sale on Campus (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Hydroponics (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Men (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Men (Box 231, Folder 8)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Men (Box 231, Folder 9)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Women (Box 231, Folder 10)
  - I (Box 231, Folder 11)
  - Institute of World Affairs (Box 231, Folder 12)
  - J (Box 231, Folder 13)
  - Jack Rice (Box 237, Folder 8)
  - Joint Committee (Box 231, Folder 14)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 231, Folder 15)
  - Journalism (Box 231, Folder 16)
  - Junior College (Box 231, Folder 17)
  - Ka (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Ki (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - La (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - Law School (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Letters, School of (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Li (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Ma (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Manspeaker, A.F. (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - Mathematics (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - Mc (Box 232, Folder 10)
  - Me (Box 232, Folder 11)
  - Medical School, September (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Medical School, October (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Medical School, November (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Medical School, December (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Medical School, January (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Medical School, February (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Medical School, March (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Medical School, April (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Medical School, May (Box 234, Folder 9)
  - Medical School, June (Box 234, Folder 10)
  - Medical School, July (Box 234, Folder 11)
  - Medical School, August (Box 234, Folder 12)
  - Medical School - Auxiliary to Stanford Clinics (Box 234, Folder 14)
  - Medical School - Institute for Industrial Hygiene (Box 234, Folder 13)
  - Medical Society - California State (Box 234, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Church (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Men's Council (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Mi (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Miogenic Laboratory (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Mo (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Museum (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - Music (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - N (Box 235, Folder 9)
  - National, September - February (Box 235, Folder 10)
  - National, March - August (Box 235, Folder 11)
  - Natural History Museum (Box 235, Folder 12)
  - Nursing (Box 234, Folder 15)
  - O (Box 235, Folder 13)
  - Pa (Box 235, Folder 14)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 235, Folder 15)
  - Passes (Box 235, Folder 16)
  - Patents (Box 235, Folder 17)
  - Pensions (Box 235, Folder 18)
  - Philosophy (Box 235, Folder 19)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Physics, September - February (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Physics, March - August (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Physiology (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Piq (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Political Science (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - President's Office (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Psychology (Box 236, Folder 8)
  - Publicity (Box 236, Folder 9)
  - Q (Box 236, Folder 10)
  - Quad (Box 236, Folder 11)
  - Questionnaires (Box 236, Folder 12)
  - Ra (Box 236, Folder 13)
  - Radio (Box 236, Folder 14)
  - Radio (Box 236, Folder 15)
  - Recommendations, Letters of (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Registrar (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions, Travel Fund - Completed (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions, Travel Fund - Pending (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Travel Fund 1939 - 40 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - Ro (Box 237, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 237, Folder 10)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 237, Folder 11)
  - Sa (Box 237, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco (Box 237, Folder 13)
  - Sc (Box 237, Folder 14)
  - Se (Box 237, Folder 15)
  - Slavic Languages (Box 237, Folder 16)
  - Sm (Box 237, Folder 17)
  - Social Science Research Committee (Box 237, Folder 18)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 237, Folder 19)
  - Social Service Board (Box 237, Folder 20)
  - Sororities (Box 237, Folder 21)
  - St (Box 237, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Associates, September - October (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Associates, November - December (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Associates, January - February (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Associates, March - April (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Associates, May - June (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Associates, July - August (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Travel Fund Requests (no funds) (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Wesley Hicks Research Fellowship (Box 234, Folder 17)
- 1940-1941, Series 25
  - A (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Academic and Alumni Secretary (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Committee - The American College and University (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - American, September - February (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - American, March - August (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - Anatomy (Box 240, Folder 7)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 240, Folder 8)
  - Assistants (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Associated Students (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Association of American Colleges (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Ba (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Bacteriology (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Be (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Bequests (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - Bi (Box 241, Folder 8)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 241, Folder 9)
  - Biology, School of (Box 241, Folder 10)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 241, Folder 11)
  - Board of Athletic Control, September - February (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Board of Athletic Control - Rose Bowl (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Br (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Bri (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Ca (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - California Emergency Relief (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - California, University of (Box 242, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 242, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Endowment (International Peace) (Box 242, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 242, Folder 10)
  - Ch (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - Chemistry (Box 242, Folder 12)
  - Civil Aeronautics Authority (Box 242, Folder 13)
  - Classics (Box 242, Folder 14)
  - Co (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Commencement (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Resources and Education (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller, September, October, November (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller, December, January, February (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller, March, April, May (Box 243, Folder 7)
  - Comptroller, June, July, August (Box 243, Folder 8)
  - Conference on the Junior College (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Conventions (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Da (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Dean of Men (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Dean of Women (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Defense (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Deferments - Selective Service (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Dentistry, College of (Box 244, Folder 9)
  - Do (Box 244, Folder 10)
  - Dormitories (Box 244, Folder 11)
  - E - Misc. (Box 245, Folder 14)
  - Economics (Box 244, Folder 12)
  - Education, School of, September - February (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of, March, April, May (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Education, School of, June, July, August (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Endowment (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Engineering - Civil (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Engineering - Electrical (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Engineering - Guggenheim Lab (Box 245, Folder 9)
  - Engineering - Mechanical (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Engineering - Military Science and Tactics (Box 245, Folder 10)
  - Engineering - Mining (Box 245, Folder 11)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 245, Folder 12)
  - English (Box 245, Folder 13)
  - Fa (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Housing (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Fellowships (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Fiftieth (Stanford 50th Anniversary) (Box 255, Folder 7)
  - Fiftieth (Stanford 50th Anniversary) - miscellaneous (Box 255, Folder 9)
  - Fiftieth (Stanford 50th Anniversary) - miscellaneous 1941 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Fiftieth (Stanford 50th Anniversary) - Symposia, etc. (Box 255, Folder 8)
  - Fiftieth: Conference on Higher Education on the Occasion of Stanford's 50th Anniversary (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Fo (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Frank F. Walker (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Fraternities (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Ga (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - General Education Board (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - Geology (Box 246, Folder 10)
  - Germanic Languages I (Box 246, Folder 11)
  - Germanic Languages II (Box 246, Folder 12)
  - Gi (Box 246, Folder 13)
  - Gr (Box 246, Folder 14)
  - Graduate School of Business, September - November (Box 246, Folder 15)
  - Graduate School of Business, December - February (Box 246, Folder 16)
  - Graduate School of Business, March - May (Box 246, Folder 17)
  - Graduate School of Business, June - August (Box 246, Folder 18)
  - Graphic Art (Box 246, Folder 19)
  - Haq (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Har (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - He (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Herbert Hoover (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 249, Folder 10)
  - History (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Ho (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Hoover Library, September - November (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - Hoover Library, December - February (Box 247, Folder 8)
  - Hoover Library, March - May (Box 247, Folder 9)
  - Hoover Library, June - August (Box 247, Folder 10)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 247, Folder 11)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Timothy (Box 247, Folder 12)
  - Houses For Sale on Campus (Box 247, Folder 13)
  - Humanities, School of (Box 247, Folder 14)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Men (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Women (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - I (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Institute of World Affairs (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - J (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, Mrs. David Starr (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - Journalism (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Ka (Box 248, Folder 8)
  - Kl (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - La (Box 248, Folder 10)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 249, Folder 11)
  - Law School (Box 248, Folder 11)
  - Legislation (Box 248, Folder 12)
  - Leland W. Cutler (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - Letters, School of (Box 248, Folder 13)
  - Li (Box 248, Folder 14)
  - Library, March - August 1940 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Library, September 1940 - February 1941 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Library, March - August 1941 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Library, September 1941 - February 1942 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Ma (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Manspeaker, Almon F. (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Mathematics (Box 249, Folder 8)
  - Mc (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - Me (Box 249, Folder 12)
  - Medical School, September 1940 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Medical School, October 1940 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - Medical School, November 1940 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Medical School, December 1940 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - Medical School, January 1941 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - Medical School, February 1941 (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - Medical School, March 1941 (Box 250, Folder 7)
  - Medical School, April 1941 (Box 250, Folder 8)
  - Medical School, May 1941 (Box 250, Folder 9)
  - Medical School, June 1941 (Box 250, Folder 10)
  - Medical School, July 1941 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - Medical School, August 1941 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - Medical School - Auxiliary to Stanford Clinics (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - Medical School - Institute of Industrial Hygiene (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Church (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - Men's Council (Box 249, Folder 9)
  - Mi (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - Mo (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Museum (Box 251, Folder 8)
  - Music (Box 251, Folder 9)
  - Music, Friends of (Box 251, Folder 10)
  - N (Box 251, Folder 11)
  - National (Box 251, Folder 12)
  - Natural History Museum (Box 251, Folder 13)
  - Nursing (Box 251, Folder 14)
  - O (Box 251, Folder 15)
  - O (Box 251, Folder 15)
  - Pa (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Passes (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Patents (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Peace Bill, The Alexander (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - Pensions (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - Philosophy (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - Physics (Box 252, Folder 9)
  - Physiology (Box 252, Folder 10)
  - Pi (Box 252, Folder 11)
  - Political Science (Box 252, Folder 12)
  - President's Office (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - President's Report (Box 253, Folder 2)